<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>GC Pod Hub</title><link>https://patlittle.github.io/GC-Pod-Hub/</link><description>Liveboat RSS Feed</description><item><title>Porter Talk #4: The Long Fight for Porters&apos; Rights</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/9b21ab00</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/9b21ab00/3c307b89.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the inhumanity of portering, and the long fight for porters’ rights. (Episode 4) Transcript]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 4 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/28ea30a3</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/28ea30a3/7a99342b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Mapping Happiness: How Where We Live Impacts Our Well-Being</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/a1bbe7b5</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a1bbe7b5/434fcb01.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[It might not surprise you that your relationships with friends and family affect your well-being. Same with your health and your job. But what about the place where you live? Whether you live in the downtown core of a major city or a commuter town or a rural community, what impact does this have on your life satisfaction, loneliness and sense of belonging? StatCan’s Lauren Pinault joins us today at the mic to explore how the places we live affect our well-being. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Calculating crop rotation for potatoes</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f67f1c9</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7f67f1c9/99d2a32e.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 12:49:27 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Lori Robinson, a 6 generation farmer in PEI, is a data hound.  As a result of her 50+ years of her and her family taking detailed notes and 20 + years of doing a four-year crop rotation system she laid the groundwork for a user-friendly calculator for crop rotations that has both economic benefits for producers and environmental benefits. Developed at the Living Labs initiative in PEI in conjunction with the PEI Potato Board, the calculator helps producers maximize profits while reducing their use of pesticides and improving soil health. And the story of the calculator has some interesting twists.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 4: How to be scam smart – Part 1</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Did you know the Government of Canada has a department that helps police gather intelligence to protect Canadians from fraud and scams? Last year, Canadians lost $569M to fraud – and that’s just what was reported! In this episode, we get tips from the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC) to protect yourself from scammers. An expert from the CAFC joins us in this collaboration episode, to discuss the various fraud and scams she sees across the Government of Canada. We learn about the warning signs to look out for in fraudulent messages, the most common types of scams, and what to do if you or a family member may have been a victim to a scam.]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>