<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>GC Pod Hub</title><link>https://patlittle.github.io/GC-Pod-Hub/</link><description>Liveboat RSS Feed</description><item><title>Porter Talk #4: The Long Fight for Porters&apos; Rights</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/9b21ab00</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/9b21ab00/3c307b89.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the inhumanity of portering, and the long fight for porters’ rights. (Episode 4) Transcript]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 4 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/28ea30a3</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/28ea30a3/7a99342b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Mapping Happiness: How Where We Live Impacts Our Well-Being</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/a1bbe7b5</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a1bbe7b5/434fcb01.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[It might not surprise you that your relationships with friends and family affect your well-being. Same with your health and your job. But what about the place where you live? Whether you live in the downtown core of a major city or a commuter town or a rural community, what impact does this have on your life satisfaction, loneliness and sense of belonging? StatCan’s Lauren Pinault joins us today at the mic to explore how the places we live affect our well-being. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Calculating crop rotation for potatoes</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f67f1c9</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7f67f1c9/99d2a32e.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 12:49:27 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Lori Robinson, a 6 generation farmer in PEI, is a data hound.  As a result of her 50+ years of her and her family taking detailed notes and 20 + years of doing a four-year crop rotation system she laid the groundwork for a user-friendly calculator for crop rotations that has both economic benefits for producers and environmental benefits. Developed at the Living Labs initiative in PEI in conjunction with the PEI Potato Board, the calculator helps producers maximize profits while reducing their use of pesticides and improving soil health. And the story of the calculator has some interesting twists.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 4: How to be scam smart – Part 1</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Did you know the Government of Canada has a department that helps police gather intelligence to protect Canadians from fraud and scams? Last year, Canadians lost $569M to fraud – and that’s just what was reported! In this episode, we get tips from the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC) to protect yourself from scammers. An expert from the CAFC joins us in this collaboration episode, to discuss the various fraud and scams she sees across the Government of Canada. We learn about the warning signs to look out for in fraudulent messages, the most common types of scams, and what to do if you or a family member may have been a victim to a scam.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Consommation de substances, stigmatisation et dépendance chez les hommes travaillant dans des métiers spécialisés</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/consommation-de-substances-stigmatisation-et-dpendance-chez-les-hommes-travaillant-dans-des-mtiers-spcialiss</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Consommation_de_substances_stigmatisation_et_dpendance_chez_les_hommes_travaillant_dans_des_mtiers_spcialiss_ep219.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 9 Jan 2025 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[La stigmatisation à l’égard de la consommation de substances influe sur la façon dont nous parlons aux personnes, sur les politiques que nous élaborons et sur la prestation des soins. Dans cet épisode, la Dre Theresa Tam, administratrice en chef de la santé publique du Canada, et Anne Tennier, présidente et première dirigeante du CCHST, discutent des façons de réduire la stigmatisation et de soutenir les hommes dans les métiers spécialisés qui font face à des difficultés.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Substance Use, Stigma and Addiction Among Men in Trades</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/substance-use-stigma-and-addiction-among-men-in-trades</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Substance_Use_Stigma_and_Addiction_Among_Men_in_Trades_ep219.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 9 Jan 2025 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Stigma surrounding substance use affects how we talk to individuals, the policies we develop, and how we provide care. In this episode, Dr. Theresa Tam, Chief Public Health Officer of Canada, and Anne Tennier, President and CEO of CCOHS, discuss ways we can reduce stigma and support men in the trades who are struggling.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #3: All Aboard the Hotel on Wheels</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/0f534256</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/0f534256/68c42f58.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:10:17 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we explore the extraordinary demands placed on sleeping car porters by rail companies and passengers while working aboard the hotel on wheels. We will also hear about the various ways these men resisted and rose above anti-Black racism. (Episode 3)Transcript]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Plant breeding: Long-game innovation in a fast-changing world</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/c0465e78</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/c0465e78/ea335723.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[How has plant breeding evolved over the past 20 years? Who are the players in Canada? What is the plant breeding continuum? And what is the proverbial sandbox in which Canadian plant breeders are working? Learn this and why it takes a special breed of innovator to become a plant-breeder. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Les principales questions sur la santé et la sécurité de 2024</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/les-principales-questions-sur-la-sant-et-la-scurit-de-2024</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode218_LesPrincipalesQuestions__FR.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 9 Dec 2024 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Chaque année, le CCHST reçoit des questions sur la santé et la sécurité de tout le Canada. Nous discutons avec l’un de nos spécialistes techniques des questions les plus importantes et les plus fréquentes de l’année.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Top Health and Safety Questions of 2024</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/top-health-and-safety-questions-of-2024</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode218_TopHealthandSafetyQuestions_EN.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 9 Dec 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ It’s the year end roundup you’ve been waiting for: the top health and safety questions you asked us in 2024.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 3 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/ce4a9565</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/ce4a9565/29f9fe00.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 4 Dec 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the dire working conditions porters experienced as they traversed the country aboard the hotel on wheels. (Episode 3 trailer)TranscriptNarrator Biographies]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Can Your Business Outsmart a Hacker?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/fbacf553</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/fbacf553/05be7b1a.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Over two thirds (70%) of Canadians experienced a cyber security incident in 2022. The strategies used by bad actors are getting more and more complex. Many of us are inundated with what feels like never-ending phishing emails, scam text messages and fraudulent phone calls. It’s rare to talk to someone who hasn’t experienced some form of a cyber attack. The situation is no different for Canadian businesses. Identity theft, scams, fraud, and ransomware are only some of the ways cyber attackers are targeting businesses today. One cyber security breach can cost a business thousands of dollars and valuable time resources to neutralize. We wanted to know: Is cyber crime on the rise in Canada? What is the relatively new phenomenon of cyber risk insurance? And in what way are consumers affected when a business experiences a security breach? The Canadian Survey of Cyber Security and Cyber Crime has published new data and, in this episode, we sat down with Howard Bilodeau, an economist at Statistics Canada to answer our questions about how cyber security is changing for businesses and what it means for the rest of us.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Prevent Slips, Trips and Falls with Good Workplace Housekeeping</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prevent-slips-trips-and-falls-with-good-workplace-housekeeping</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode217_SlipsTripsFalls_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:38:55 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Good workplace housekeeping might seem like a simple concept, but it doesn’t always get the respect it deserves. Learn how effective housekeeping can reduce the risk of slips, trips and falls, one of the most common lost-time injuries.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Prévenir les glissades, trébuchements et chutes grâce à une bonne tenue des locaux de travail</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prvenir-les-glissades-trbuchements-et-chutes-grce-une-bonne-tenue-des-locaux-de-travail</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode217_Glissades_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:36:14 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[La bonne tenue des locaux de travail peut sembler un concept simple, mais elle n’est pas toujours reconnue à sa juste valeur. Découvrez comment une tenue efficace des locaux peut réduire le risque de glissades, de trébuchements et de chutes, qui sont à l’origine de blessures entraînant une absence au travail parmi les plus courantes. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #2: Who Were the Porters?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/52bae4d3</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/52bae4d3/151f8563.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:49:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is AI Coming For Your Job?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/8b36bff9</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/8b36bff9/074edef7.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 3 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[AI is here and it’s here to stay. Apps like ChatGPT are now allowing us to perform complex tasks with the click of a button.  As we begin to use these new versions of AI, our jobs are destined to change. So, what will an average day of work look like a decade from now? Which jobs will AI impact the most? And is AI coming to replace our jobs altogether?   In this episode, we sat down with AI expert Tahsin Mehdi, an economist in the social analysis and modeling division of Statistics Canada, to answer our questions about how AI will transform our work lives in Canada. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 2 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/958a8685</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/958a8685/8cb11753.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:01:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2 trailer) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Protecting Workers from Bird Flu</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protecting-workers-from-bird-flu</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode216_ProtectingWorkersFromBirdFlu_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:36:05 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Farms experiencing a surge in bird flu infections can put people who work with poultry and dairy cattle at risk of catching the illness. In this episode, we talk with CCOHS Senior Technical Specialist Matea Kokorovic about measures you can take to protect your workers.Released: September 13, 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Protéger les travailleurs contre la grippe aviaire</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protger-les-travailleurs-contre-la-grippe-aviaire</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode216_Protger_les_travailleurs_contre_la_grippe_aviaire_working_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:32:29 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Les exploitations qui connaissent une recrudescence des infections par la grippe aviaire exposent les personnes qui travaillent avec les volailles et les bovins laitiers au risque de contracter la maladie. Au cours du présent épisode, nous nous entretenons avec Matea Kokorovic, spécialiste technique principale du Centre canadien d’hygiène et de sécurité au travail au sujet des mesures que vous pouvez prendre pour protéger vos travailleurs.Date de diffusion : 13 septembre 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #1: Honouring Stanley G. Grizzle - An Activist For Our Times</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/483c1bfa</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/483c1bfa/46a12ede.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:22:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the life of the man who recorded the stories of the porters working on the rails. (Episode 1) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 1 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/69f33af4</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/69f33af4/8a4d3c66.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:11:58 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the man who turned the microphone over to the porters to record their experiences working on the rails. (Episode 1 trailer)]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/fb5f3d58</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/fb5f3d58/542042d8.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:42:21 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Their voices, along with those of their wives and children, relay stories of both hardship and resilience. (Podcast series trailer)]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/sparking-courageous-conversations-at-work</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode215__CourageousConversations_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 8 Aug 2024 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ Holding courageous conversations in the workplace can help to advance equity, diversity, and inclusion. Learn how to start these discussions, and how they can foster greater understanding, connection, growth, and even healing. Released:  August 8, 2024 -------------------------« Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work »     Tenir des conversations courageuses sur le lieu de travail peut contribuer à faire avancer l’équité, la diversité et l’inclusion. Apprenez comment entamer ces discussions et comment elles peuvent favoriser une meilleure compréhension, une meilleure connexion, une meilleure croissance et même une meilleure guérison.Date de diffusion : 8 août 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Why Economists Are Sounding the Alarm on Productivity</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7b2071ff</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7b2071ff/7f86ea5b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Canada’s workforce is among the most educated in the world. But when it comes to worker productivity, we’ve seen a real slump over the past few years. The quarterly data published by StatCan in June 2024 confirms Canadian workers are continuing to underperform compared to our neighbours to the south. This comes as no surprise to this episode’s guest, Guy Gellatly, Chief Economic Advisor at StatCan. The latest quarterly numbers are a continuation of an on-going decline in Canada’s productivity that economists have been tracking for years.  But what factors influence worker productivity? And why does it matter if Canadians are less productive? As a matter of fact, what even  productivity? In this episode, we asked Guy to help us understand how we got to this point and why it matters for Canadians.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Science vs. food waste</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f8e0c6e</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7f8e0c6e/41a008b7.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Can we make biodegradable plastics using food waste? Can we control disease in crops and eliminate food borne pathogens using just hydrogen peroxide, ozone and UV rays? Yes, we can! Meet the two grand prize winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge – in the novel technology stream -- who proved we can do this and more. Learn how Genecis Bioindustries and Clean Works are fighting food waste and food loss with cutting-edge science. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Exploring the intersection between IP law and the protection of Indigenous knowledge and cultural expressions.</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/exploring-the-intersection-between-ip-law-and-the-protection-of-indigenous-knowledge-and-cultural-expressions-6_dwPtEd</link><author>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/7dc0fbc6-bf76-42af-9a5a-54b585cf7862/audio/6d7173e5-5d2c-40ed-9eac-97249d398041/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jun 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What’s an urban forest?</title><link>https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/whats-an-urban-forest</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/1836700347-nrcan-whats-an-urban-forest.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jun 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science">Simply Science</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>It&apos;s Not Easy Bein&apos; Green</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/54f7dce8</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/54f7dce8/a10b6988.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jun 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[We can try our best, but its not always easy knowing what's best for the environment. The world is complicated, and it isn't as simple as reduce, reuse, recycle—though that's a great place to start!In the immortal words of Kermit the Frog, "It's not easy bein' green."We have two stories exploring that theme. The first is one we made in-house asking just how green our digital world really is, and the second comes from the Simply Science podcast exploring the world of urban forests.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/how-plain-language-improves-workplace-health-and-safety</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode214_PlainLanguage_JocelynPletz_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 5 Jun 2024 14:53:52 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[When employers commit to using plain language, they make it easier for workers to do their jobs. They also help to support a more inclusive workplace. In this episode, we talk with plain language expert Jocelyn Pletz about how clear and simple communication can improve health and safety.-------------------------« How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety »   Lorsque les employeurs s’engagent à utiliser un langage clair, ils facilitent le travail des travailleurs. Ils favorisent aussi l’inclusivité dans le milieu de travail. Dans cet épisode, nous parlerons avec Jocelyn Pletz, spécialiste du langage clair, qui expliquera comment les communications claires et simples peuvent améliorer la santé et la sécurité.Date de diffusion : 5 juin 2024Taille du fichier : 8.2 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Embracing Neurodiversity in the Workplace</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/embracing-neurodiversity-in-the-workplace</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode213_Neurodiversity.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 20:09:44 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ In this episode, we chat with Dr. Marie-Hélène Pelletier, a psychologist and business leader, about embracing neurodiverse conditions such as attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, dyslexia, and autism spectrum disorder, in the workplace.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Faire place à la neurodiversité au travail</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/faire-place-la-neurodiversit-au-travail</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode213_Faire_place__la_neurodiversit_au_travail_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 19:58:38 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Dans cet épisode, nous discutons avec Marie-Hélène Pelletier, Ph. D., psychologue et chef des opérations, au sujet d’adaptation à la neurodiversité, comme le trouble d’hyperactivité avec déficit de l’attention, la dyslexie et le trouble du spectre de l’autisme en milieu de travailDate de diffusion : 13 may 2024 Taille du fichier :  8 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Why Food Inflation Is Such a Hard Nut to Crack</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/97b2d26e</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/97b2d26e/2f703e92.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 8 May 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you feeling like it's a little bit harder to bring home the bacon... from the grocery store? The latest data indicate that food prices have mostly stabilized... but why does it feel like the cost of feeding your family is still going up?Today we're talking food inflation with StatCan's resident smart cookie Taylor Mitchell.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How the IP agent profession is regulated</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-the-ip-agent-profession-is-regulated-2LEqe6Zv</link><author>CPATA, College of Patent Agents &amp; Trademark Agents, Canadian Intellectual Property Office, CIPO</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/bd69a14a-17bb-4f9d-b562-95a58d2d0cb5/audio/0b43c574-3324-4a8e-8017-28381ef6786b/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 1 May 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Juda Strawczynski, CEO and Registrar of the College of Patent Agents and Trademark Agents (CPATA) explains how CPATA regulates the IP agent profession, ensuring that patent agents and trademark agents deliver accessible, ethical and expert IP services in Canada.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Challenge accepted!</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/0a6bab0c</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/0a6bab0c/8897684b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:20:54 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Announcing the two winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge (Business Models Stream)Two companies took away $1.5 M! Find out who they are. Learn what it took to become the winners of the challenge, and leaders in this new sub-sector. The funds will help the winning companies further expand their success in fighting food waste and reducing greenhouse gases.  And, we’ll give you a glimpse behind the scenes with Dr Jean-Charles Le Vallée, who will share insights into being a jury member of the challenge. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Treasures Revealed: Episode 16</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/81acd6cf</link><author>Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/81acd6cf/d5bc821b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The hammering of the last spike into the Canadian Pacific Railway expanded access to the nation immeasurably, physically and symbolically connecting it from coast to coast. While seen as a victory in the dominant narrative of Canada, it served as a catalyst for the mass displacement of Indigenous peoples and the exploitation and even death of labourers involved in the construction of the railway. Join us as Marcelle Cinq-Mars delves into the historic image depicting this moment, and we reflect on the real human cost that was paid in the name of progress.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>It&apos;s 8 pm...Do You Know What Your Kids Are Googling?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/8710dcf9</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/8710dcf9/cb577436.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 9 Apr 2024 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[StatCan released new analysis into the online culture our kids are growing up in, and it’s far from the best of all possible worlds: misinformation, bullying, violence… and worse.Analyst Rachel Tsitomeneas joins us to dive into the findings. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/day-of-mourning-melanie-kowalski-flemings-story</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode212_Melanie_Kowalski-Fleming_DayOfMourning.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 8 Apr 2024 14:07:32 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA["Mark was not one to go to the hospital. If he could duct tape or crazy glue it to fix it, he would. This was so much more than what duct tape or crazy glue could fix.” Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s life changed forever the day her husband fell off a ladder at work. Hear her powerful story. -------------------------« Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story »« Mark n’était pas du genre à aller à l’hôpital. S’il pouvait régler le problème avec du ruban adhésif ou de la colle, il le faisait. Mais cette fois, le ruban adhésif et la colle n’y pouvaient rien. » La vie de Melanie Kowalski-Fleming a changé pour toujours le jour où son mari est tombé d’une échelle au travail. Écoutez son histoire percutante.Date de diffusion : 8 avril 2024Taille du fichier : 7.5 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What innovators need to know about the Competition Bureau</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/what-innovators-need-to-know-about-the-competition-bureau-Tjj37JmI</link><author>Canadian Bureau of Competition, Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/02a3fbe4-ec94-454b-8f88-e8e915b5d2ff/audio/c37de1ae-aee8-45d2-8983-0032d1bf6350/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 3 Apr 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Alan Gunderson, senior economist and coordinator at the Economic Analysis Directorate at the Competition Bureau explains the Bureau’s mandate and actions when it comes to intellectual property.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Tax time: What older Canadians and caregivers need to know</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/tax-time-what-older-canadians-and-caregivers-need-to-know-u7OhrWN9</link><author>Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/18f63d87-fb0c-4903-af7e-e088670d5494/audio/01714c8e-0da8-4388-b47e-52407fcdd27b/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the importance of filing your taxes on time, what tax credits are available for older Canadians and caregivers for the 2023 filing season, tips to help with filing, important dates and the CRA’s toll-free number, 1-800-959-8281.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Période des impôts : Ce que les aînés canadiens et les proches aidants doivent savoir</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/periode-des-impots-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-et-les-proches-aidants-doivent-savoir-SbfA8SpQ</link><author>Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/0a89e7b2-4fbf-4612-b70b-ab532098dcd6/audio/4c4fd677-5fb8-498e-be3b-f20c6524efae/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:19:26 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Découvrez l’importance de produire votre déclaration de revenus dans les temps et quels crédits d’impôt sont offerts aux aînés canadiens et aux proches aidants pour la période des impôts 2023. Obtenez également des conseils pour vous aider à produire votre déclaration et apprenez quelles sont les dates importantes. Voici le numéro sans frais de l’ARC : 1-800-959-7383.Page Facebook des Aînés au Canada - https://www.facebook.com/AinesauCanada/]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Combattre la fraude en la reconnaissant : Ce que les aînés canadiens doivent savoir</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/combattre-la-fraude-en-la-reconnaissant-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-doivent-savoir-45XxdLpc</link><author>Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/68d929e0-f1da-4c9c-b21c-8dc3b517f4ee/audio/08552b08-191a-4913-9b01-141f73c441a5/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:50:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury et Jeffrey Horncastle parlent du Centre antifraude du Canada, des principales fraudes envers les aînés canadiens, des mesures à prendre si vous êtes victime de fraude et de l’importance de signaler une fraude au Centre antifraude du Canada, soit en ligne ou en appelant le numéro sans frais 1-888-495-8501.Centre antifraude du Canada : Mois de la prévention de la fraude :Guide de sécurité à l’intention des aînés, GRC :]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Fighting fraud with knowledge: What older Canadians need to know</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/fighting-fraud-with-knowledge-what-older-canadians-need-to-know-74Z9Ffwc</link><author>Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/54c95db9-0ac5-4904-aed0-49469626d84a/audio/b3aa55bd-4ee5-43f7-87b6-920c070d14be/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:49:55 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury and Jeffrey Horncastle discuss the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC), tops scams targeting older Canadians, what to do if you have been a victim of fraud and the importance of reporting fraud to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre online or by calling the toll-free number at 1-888-495-8501.Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre: RCMP Seniors Guide to Safety and Security:]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How Do You Say &quot;Language Revitalization&quot; in Cree?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/bd75c457</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/bd75c457/f67c653e.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[More than 70 distinct Indigenous languages are spoken by First Nations people, Métis and Inuit in Canada, but these languages are under threat. In this episode, we speak with Randy Morin and Belinda kakiyosēw Daniels, who share their knowledge of the Cree language with learners at the Nêhiyawak Language Experience, about the wisdom encoded in Indigenous languages, as well as the opportunities for these languages and the barriers they face. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Comprendre les effets de la sensibilité aux parfums</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/comprendre-les-effets-de-la-sensibilit-aux-parfums</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode211_Comprendre_les_effets_de_la_sensibilit__aux_parfums.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Pour certains travailleurs, l’eau de Cologne et les crèmes à mains peuvent sentir bon, mais pour leurs collègues qui présentent une sensibilité aux parfums, elles peuvent avoir des effets désagréables pour la santé. En fait, les réactions aux parfums, comme les maux de tête, les démangeaisons oculaires et les difficultés respiratoires, sont un problème de santé, et elles sont considérées comme une déficience au sens de la Loi canadienne sur les droits de la personne.   Date de diffusion : 18 mars 2024  Taille du fichier : 3.3 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Making Sense of Scent Sensitivities</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/making-sense-of-scent-sensitivities</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode211_ScentsSensitivites.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ While the scent of cologne or hand lotion may be pleasant to some, for co-workers with sensitivities to fragrances, they may have unpleasant health effects. In fact, reactions to scents, such as headaches, itchy eyes, and difficulty breathing, are a medical condition and recognized disability under the Canada Human Rights Act.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is that a robot in your field?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/a5bf9d8e</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a5bf9d8e/3ef448b2.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Ag-robotics specialists Chuck Baresich believes you’ll have a robot in your field sooner than you think.  What will they do? How will they add value to your farm? Chuck paints a picture of that future. And what is the government doing to help the agricultural sector be ready for those robots? Marco Valicenti, Director General of Innovation Programs Directorate and Brett Maxwell, Director of Strategic Policy Branch explain how Agriculture and Agri-Food Canada’s programs are enabling that future.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is natural hydrogen the solution?</title><link>https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/is-natural-hydrogen-the-solution</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/1769171136-nrcan-is-natural-hydrogen-the-solution.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science">Simply Science</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How does IP fit into the world of scientific research and experimental development?</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-does-ip-fit-into-the-world-of-scientific-research-and-experimental-development-KJ3yT3ka</link><author>Canada Revenue Agency, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/6265bedc-d3df-40c7-9411-c6d07ad4f1b0/audio/3340bdc5-461c-4494-adfb-af6b9b0f8ac1/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 6 Mar 2024 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[David Arsenault, Atlantic Regional Manager for the Canada Revenue Agency's Scientific Research and Experimental Development (SR&ED) Tax Incentive Program, demystifies the parallel worlds of R&D and IP from an SR&ED tax incentive program perspective.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 3: Platform economy and you!</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-3-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-3-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[It's easy to get lost in an internet rabbit hole when trying to learn about the "platform economy" and what it means for your taxes. Whether you're a rideshare driver, a video game streamer, or a social media influencer, this episode has something for you! Originally recorded in 2023.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Hiring smart</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/3fa7c93f</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/3fa7c93f/85427ea6.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Hear from two innovators who are successfully tackling labor shortages in our sector: one at the national level with an all-encompassing, all-stakeholders-engaged strategy; and the other on a regional level with a smart program for hiring and settling new immigrants into a rural community.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 2: TFSA vs. RRSP, what&apos;s the difference?</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-2-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-2-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you saving for that next car or trip? Maybe even thinking about retiring early? In this episode, our CRA experts explain the basics of a Tax-Free Savings Account (TFSA) and a Registered Retirement Savings Plan (RRSP). We'll dive into the differences between the two and answer the most frequently asked questions. Originally recorded in 2023.]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>