<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>GC Pod Hub</title><link>https://patlittle.github.io/GC-Pod-Hub/</link><description>Liveboat RSS Feed</description><item><title>Security Awareness (COR310)</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z2I0idihsAQ</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Z2I0idihsAQ?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 7 Feb 2025 16:24:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[To take the training: https://catalogue.csps-efpc.gc.ca/product?catalog=COR310&cm_locale=en 
General public access to the training: https://opn.csps-efpc.gc.ca/viewer/COR310-EN

This video was produced by the Communications team at the Treasury Board of Canada Secretariat.

This video is also available in French: https://youtu.be/5ZfM9VskZMY]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Discussion avec Natan Obed au sujet de la politique sur l’Inuit Nunangat</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UUZG7h72cdw</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/UUZG7h72cdw?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cette vidéo présente une discussion avec Natan Obed, président de l’Inuit Tapiriit Kanatami, sur les principes clés de la politique sur l’Inuit Nunangat, les obligations connexes des fonctionnaires et la manière dont ces derniers peuvent faire avancer la réconciliation en intégrant ces obligations à leur travail au quotidien.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/nunangat-policy-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>A Conversation with Natan Obed About the Inuit Nunangat Policy</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hAHWsE6Ybgs</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/hAHWsE6Ybgs?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 15:39:46 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video presents a conversation with Natan Obed, President of Inuit Tapiriit Kanatami, about the key principles of the Inuit Nunangat Policy, the obligations of public servants, and how they can advance reconciliation by integrating these obligations into their daily work.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/nunangat-policy-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Cape Smokey – Ingonish, Nova Scotia</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_eUIa093dA</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-_eUIa093dA?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cape Smokey ski hill in Cape Breton is upgrading its power systems from the mid-point to the top of the hill to meet growing energy needs, make more snow, and phase out diesel for cleaner air and less noise. 

Transcription
Cape Smokey is making more snow and more tourism opportunities with more efficient energy. New, modern power systems at the ski hill will help meet energy and snowmaking needs while replacing diesel, for cleaner air and less noise. 
Investing in clean growth pays off:  new markets, more jobs, accelerated growth, while minimizing environmental impacts.  
SMEs like Cape Smokey are leading the way by adopting new technologies and approaches to doing business.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #4: The Long Fight for Porters&apos; Rights</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/9b21ab00</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/9b21ab00/3c307b89.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 13:11:40 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the inhumanity of portering, and the long fight for porters’ rights. (Episode 4) Transcript]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What are Tariffs?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-IW_ODQ6Qeg</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-IW_ODQ6Qeg?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 3 Feb 2025 18:48:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[What are tariffs? 
Tariffs are taxes or duties that countries apply to imports. They don’t appear on sales receipts.  

Why do countries use tariffs? 
To raise revenue for public services and/ or to protect domestic production by making foreign goods more expensive. 

How do tariffs affect me?  
Tariffs can impact the prices you pay at the store. When the cost of importing goods increases, businesses pass the bulk of this cost onto consumers.  

Why do Canada’s free trade agreements matter?  
Canada’s 15 free trade agreements provide Canadians with tariff-free access to nearly all products traded between Canada and its free-trade partners. This helps Canadian businesses access markets in over 50 countries representing 1.5 billion consumers and keeps us connected to the world. 

For more information: https://www.canada.ca/unitedstatestariffs]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 4 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/28ea30a3</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/28ea30a3/7a99342b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Mapping Happiness: How Where We Live Impacts Our Well-Being</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/a1bbe7b5</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a1bbe7b5/434fcb01.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[It might not surprise you that your relationships with friends and family affect your well-being. Same with your health and your job. But what about the place where you live? Whether you live in the downtown core of a major city or a commuter town or a rural community, what impact does this have on your life satisfaction, loneliness and sense of belonging? StatCan’s Lauren Pinault joins us today at the mic to explore how the places we live affect our well-being. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Série Réflexions sur le leadership des sous-ministres : Margaret Bloodworth</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rnolFchnChs</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/rnolFchnChs?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cette vidéo met en vedette Margaret Bloodworth, conseillère nationale pour la sécurité auprès du premier ministre et secrétaire associée du Cabinet à la retraite, qui livre ses réflexions sur le processus décisionnel durant les événements du 11 septembre, offre des conseils sur les périodes de transition au sein du gouvernement et donne son point de vue sur la façon de diriger une organisation.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/margaret-bloodworth-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Deputy Minister Leadership Reflections Series: Margaret Bloodworth</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZj5Z71UUDU</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/HZj5Z71UUDU?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video features Margaret Bloodworth, retired National Security Advisor to the Prime Minister and Associate Secretary to the Cabinet, who reflects on the decision-making process during 9/11, offers guidance on government transition periods, and provides her insights on how to lead an organization.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/margaret-bloodworth-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Calculating crop rotation for potatoes</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f67f1c9</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7f67f1c9/99d2a32e.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 12:49:27 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Lori Robinson, a 6 generation farmer in PEI, is a data hound.  As a result of her 50+ years of her and her family taking detailed notes and 20 + years of doing a four-year crop rotation system she laid the groundwork for a user-friendly calculator for crop rotations that has both economic benefits for producers and environmental benefits. Developed at the Living Labs initiative in PEI in conjunction with the PEI Potato Board, the calculator helps producers maximize profits while reducing their use of pesticides and improving soil health. And the story of the calculator has some interesting twists.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>G7 2025 Short Logo Reveal</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dUjkNzkL_FI</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/dUjkNzkL_FI?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[G7 2025 Kananaskis Short Logo Reveal
Showing scenic shots of a mountain in the Kananaskis area with a river and forest in the foreground, overlaid at the end with the G7 2025 Kananaskis logo featuring a grey stylized image of a mountain and a green pine tree with seven branches. The video is accompanied by background music.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 4: How to be scam smart – Part 1</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-4-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Did you know the Government of Canada has a department that helps police gather intelligence to protect Canadians from fraud and scams? Last year, Canadians lost $569M to fraud – and that’s just what was reported! In this episode, we get tips from the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC) to protect yourself from scammers. An expert from the CAFC joins us in this collaboration episode, to discuss the various fraud and scams she sees across the Government of Canada. We learn about the warning signs to look out for in fraudulent messages, the most common types of scams, and what to do if you or a family member may have been a victim to a scam.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Consommation de substances, stigmatisation et dépendance chez les hommes travaillant dans des métiers spécialisés</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/consommation-de-substances-stigmatisation-et-dpendance-chez-les-hommes-travaillant-dans-des-mtiers-spcialiss</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Consommation_de_substances_stigmatisation_et_dpendance_chez_les_hommes_travaillant_dans_des_mtiers_spcialiss_ep219.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 9 Jan 2025 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[La stigmatisation à l’égard de la consommation de substances influe sur la façon dont nous parlons aux personnes, sur les politiques que nous élaborons et sur la prestation des soins. Dans cet épisode, la Dre Theresa Tam, administratrice en chef de la santé publique du Canada, et Anne Tennier, présidente et première dirigeante du CCHST, discutent des façons de réduire la stigmatisation et de soutenir les hommes dans les métiers spécialisés qui font face à des difficultés.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Substance Use, Stigma and Addiction Among Men in Trades</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/substance-use-stigma-and-addiction-among-men-in-trades</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Substance_Use_Stigma_and_Addiction_Among_Men_in_Trades_ep219.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 9 Jan 2025 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Stigma surrounding substance use affects how we talk to individuals, the policies we develop, and how we provide care. In this episode, Dr. Theresa Tam, Chief Public Health Officer of Canada, and Anne Tennier, President and CEO of CCOHS, discuss ways we can reduce stigma and support men in the trades who are struggling.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Deputy Minister Leadership Reflections Series: Rob Fonberg</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zdl6X_Vk3W8</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zdl6X_Vk3W8?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 7 Jan 2025 14:36:32 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video features Rob Fonberg, retired Deputy Minister of National Defence and Special Advisor to the Clerk of the Privy Council, who provides insight on the difference between policy and advice, offers guidance to young public servants, and reflects on turning work into passion. 

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/rob-fonberg-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Série Réflexions sur le leadership des sous-ministres : Rob Fonberg</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f5qEhFJaIK4</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/f5qEhFJaIK4?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 7 Jan 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cette vidéo met en vedette Rob Fonberg, ancien sous-ministre de Défense nationale et conseiller spécial auprès du greffier du Conseil privé, qui présente ses idées sur la différence entre politiques et avis, offre des conseils aux jeunes fonctionnaires et livre ses réflexions sur la façon de transformer son travail en passion.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/rob-fonberg-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Team Canada Trade Missions – 2024 edition</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izWmu8J9pF0</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/izWmu8J9pF0?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[In 2024, Canada led trade missions to Malaysia, Vietnam, South Korea, Indonesia, and the Philippines as part of Canada’s Indo-Pacific Strategy. 
 
These trade missions open doors for companies and organizations to broaden their reach and unlock new opportunities while helping Canada expand trade, investment, and supply chain resilience and deepening connections with the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) and the broader Indo-Pacific region. 
 
Learn more about Canada’s Team Canada Trade Missions: https://www.international.gc.ca/trade-commerce/trade_events-evenements_commerciaux/trade_missions-missions_commerciales/about-a_propos.aspx?lang=eng  
 
#GoTeamCanadaTrade #IndoPacific #IndoPacificStrategy]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Governing in a Complex World Series: Explaining the Global Polycrisis</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=il-Yw8jPLAg</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/il-Yw8jPLAg?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:07:17 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This event recording explains what a global polycrisis is, how it impacts governance systems, and what this means for the Government of Canada.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/governing-complex-world-series/global-polycrisis-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Série sur la gouvernance dans un monde complexe : Comprendre ce qu&apos;est la polycrise mondiale</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NvFey5JDGUc</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/NvFey5JDGUc?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:04:58 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cet enregistrement d'événement explique en quoi consiste une polycrise mondiale, les répercussions d'une telle crise sur les systèmes de gouvernance et ce que cela signifie pour le gouvernement du Canada.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/governing-complex-world-series/global-polycrisis-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #3: All Aboard the Hotel on Wheels</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/0f534256</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/0f534256/68c42f58.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:10:17 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we explore the extraordinary demands placed on sleeping car porters by rail companies and passengers while working aboard the hotel on wheels. We will also hear about the various ways these men resisted and rose above anti-Black racism. (Episode 3)Transcript]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Plant breeding: Long-game innovation in a fast-changing world</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/c0465e78</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/c0465e78/ea335723.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 12:32:57 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[How has plant breeding evolved over the past 20 years? Who are the players in Canada? What is the plant breeding continuum? And what is the proverbial sandbox in which Canadian plant breeders are working? Learn this and why it takes a special breed of innovator to become a plant-breeder. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Les principales questions sur la santé et la sécurité de 2024</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/les-principales-questions-sur-la-sant-et-la-scurit-de-2024</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode218_LesPrincipalesQuestions__FR.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 9 Dec 2024 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Chaque année, le CCHST reçoit des questions sur la santé et la sécurité de tout le Canada. Nous discutons avec l’un de nos spécialistes techniques des questions les plus importantes et les plus fréquentes de l’année.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Top Health and Safety Questions of 2024</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/top-health-and-safety-questions-of-2024</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode218_TopHealthandSafetyQuestions_EN.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 9 Dec 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ It’s the year end roundup you’ve been waiting for: the top health and safety questions you asked us in 2024.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 3 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/ce4a9565</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/ce4a9565/29f9fe00.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 4 Dec 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Join us as we delve into the dire working conditions porters experienced as they traversed the country aboard the hotel on wheels. (Episode 3 trailer)TranscriptNarrator Biographies]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Advice for safe travel outside of Canada</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i39Xw6XSzIM</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/i39Xw6XSzIM?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 4 Dec 2024 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Deputy Minister Leadership Reflections Series: Yaprak Baltacioğlu</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K88QLmNU_zw</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/K88QLmNU_zw?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 4 Dec 2024 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video features Yaprak Baltacioğlu, retired Secretary of the Treasury Board, who reflects on her personal journey in the public service, provides insight on the importance of professional relationships built on trust and respect, and shares her passion for making real change in Canada. 

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/index-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Série Réflexions sur le leadership des sous-ministres : Yaprak Baltacioğlu</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NQxkjpWR8jA</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/NQxkjpWR8jA?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 4 Dec 2024 11:48:21 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cette vidéo met en vedette Yaprak Baltacioğlu, secrétaire du Conseil du Trésor à la retraite, qui livre ses réflexions sur son parcours personnel dans la fonction publique, explique l'importance des relations professionnelles reposant sur la confiance et le respect et parle de sa passion en vue d'apporter un changement réel au Canada. 

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/yaprak-baltacioglu-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Futurism for policy makers</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AJyDaNVzH3Q</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/AJyDaNVzH3Q?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 3 Dec 2024 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This event recording features applied health futurist Dr. Zayna Khayat, who shares insights from her extensive experience in futurism and provides practical strategies for integrating it into policy work, particularly for public servants.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/policy-makers-futurism-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>La futurologie au service de l’élaboration de politiques</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUJ7uPqSqHo</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/YUJ7uPqSqHo?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 3 Dec 2024 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cet enregistrement d'événement met en vedette Zayna Khayat, Ph. D., futurologue spécialiste de la recherche appliquée en santé, qui présente des observations découlant de son expérience considérable dans le domaine de la futurologie et propose des conseils pratiques aux fonctionnaires pour les aider à intégrer la futurologie à leur travail concernant les politiques.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/policy-makers-futurism-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Bear River First Nation, N.S.</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TgflBf32oz0</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/TgflBf32oz0?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 2 Dec 2024 17:57:17 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re grateful for projects that connect us to the earth and one another. Bear River First Nation, #Mikmaki is embracing those connections to drive economic development.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Town of Salisbury’s new amphitheatre - NB</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0CvpVm1yA6c</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/0CvpVm1yA6c?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 2 Dec 2024 17:52:13 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Salisbury will soon host a variety of events, bringing people together in their new, vibrant community space. From concerts to community gatherings, the Salisbury amphitheatre is set to become a cornerstone of local entertainment and engagement. Plus, with the addition of a new trail system for walking and biking, there's even more to explore and enjoy. #gc 

Transcript:
So, we've had this dream for many, many years. But of course, it takes funding to do these types of things. 
And as a small community, we don't always have the resources to make these things happen. 
So obviously when we approached ACOA with the idea and the relevance as well as the opportunities and the benefits for our community ACOA came forward obviously with funding.
The importance of the amphitheater as well as the connecting trail to our residents is something that they've been asking for for many, many years.
As Canada's most active community in 2023, we show that having a very connected community is important where people can walk trails and do recreational activities.
The amphitheater was one of those where we could bring people together in our community, connecting place where we can grow as one. And we're just so thrilled to have this happening in our community.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Lisa Qiluqqi Koperqualuk on Arctic Security</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lE8qcT987qQ</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/lE8qcT987qQ?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video features Lisa Qiluqqi Koperqualuk, President of the Inuit Circumpolar Council Canada, who shares her insights on Inuit perspectives and leadership in the context of geopolitical and security issues in the Canadian Arctic.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/arctic-security-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Lisa Qiluqqi Koperqualuk sur la Sécurité en Arctique</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GvM3K7gu4h4</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/GvM3K7gu4h4?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cette vidéo met en vedette Lisa Qiluqqi Koperqualuk, présidente du Conseil circumpolaire inuit du Canada, qui fait part de ses réflexions au sujet des perspectives et du leadership inuit dans le contexte des questions géopolitiques et de sécurité dans l'Arctique canadien.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/arctic-security-fra.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Can Your Business Outsmart a Hacker?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/fbacf553</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/fbacf553/05be7b1a.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Over two thirds (70%) of Canadians experienced a cyber security incident in 2022. The strategies used by bad actors are getting more and more complex. Many of us are inundated with what feels like never-ending phishing emails, scam text messages and fraudulent phone calls. It’s rare to talk to someone who hasn’t experienced some form of a cyber attack. The situation is no different for Canadian businesses. Identity theft, scams, fraud, and ransomware are only some of the ways cyber attackers are targeting businesses today. One cyber security breach can cost a business thousands of dollars and valuable time resources to neutralize. We wanted to know: Is cyber crime on the rise in Canada? What is the relatively new phenomenon of cyber risk insurance? And in what way are consumers affected when a business experiences a security breach? The Canadian Survey of Cyber Security and Cyber Crime has published new data and, in this episode, we sat down with Howard Bilodeau, an economist at Statistics Canada to answer our questions about how cyber security is changing for businesses and what it means for the rest of us.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Deputy Minister Leadership Reflections Series: Defining leadership</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NkE0wOobqBo</link><author>Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/NkE0wOobqBo?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7v7PBgbsatDzXMim2yF5rQ">Canada School of PS / École de la FP du Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This video features excerpts from interviews with six former deputy ministers, who share what leadership means to them and how it can be applied in the public service.

https://www.csps-efpc.gc.ca/video/dm-leadership-reflections-series/defining-leadership-eng.aspx]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Prevent Slips, Trips and Falls with Good Workplace Housekeeping</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prevent-slips-trips-and-falls-with-good-workplace-housekeeping</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode217_SlipsTripsFalls_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:38:55 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Good workplace housekeeping might seem like a simple concept, but it doesn’t always get the respect it deserves. Learn how effective housekeeping can reduce the risk of slips, trips and falls, one of the most common lost-time injuries.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Prévenir les glissades, trébuchements et chutes grâce à une bonne tenue des locaux de travail</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/prvenir-les-glissades-trbuchements-et-chutes-grce-une-bonne-tenue-des-locaux-de-travail</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode217_Glissades_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:36:14 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[La bonne tenue des locaux de travail peut sembler un concept simple, mais elle n’est pas toujours reconnue à sa juste valeur. Découvrez comment une tenue efficace des locaux peut réduire le risque de glissades, de trébuchements et de chutes, qui sont à l’origine de blessures entraînant une absence au travail parmi les plus courantes. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>GC Digital Talent Platform Instructional Video</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8u8bWujSZio</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/8u8bWujSZio?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 20:43:38 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The GC Digital Talent platform instructional video helps individuals create a profile and navigate through the process to apply for digital talent opportunities in the Government of Canada. 

This video is also available in French: https://youtu.be/SD794Uv8K6A]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Minister Ng shares how CPTPP impacts Canadians and the world</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CbUiY3ambxU</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/CbUiY3ambxU?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[In 2 weeks, Canada will welcome fellow Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership (CPTPP) members in Vancouver for the #CPTPP Commission Meeting. 

As we look forward to this important event, listen in as Minister Ng shares how CPTPP impacts Canadians and the world.  

#CPTPPCanada2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>BioAccelerator Groundbreaking - PEI</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M27SnLTJAww</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/M27SnLTJAww?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:34:55 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Congratulations to the PEI BioAlliance on the official groundbreaking of the BioAccelerator! 🔬🧪🧬 

Learn more about the new facility that is propelling the region’s bioscience cluster forward: https://peibioalliance.com/news/government-industry-partnership-breaks-ground-on-50-million-bioaccelerator/

Transcript
BIOACCELERATOR GROUNDBREAKING

The P.E.I. BioAlliance has broken ground on the BioAccelerator, a 60,000 sq. ft. facility that will provide essential infrastructure for the region’s bioscience and life sciences industry.

Expected to be completed in 2026, the facility will be occupied by researchers, entrepreneurs, and bioscience-based companies.

PEI’s bioscience community is widely recognized for its collaborative economic cluster model that drives innovation and sector growth.

The sector now includes 60 bioscience companies earning over $600 million annually in sales, making bioscience the second-largest industry in P.E.I.

The PEI Bioscience Cluster has surpassed 2025 growth targets and is well on its way to becoming a billion-dollar industry by 2030.

ACOA is proud to support this major advancement in Prince Edward Island’s bioscience innovation ecosystem!]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>The Fredericton Pickleball Club - New Brunswick</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJNTOnFib2c</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/gJNTOnFib2c?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 6 Nov 2024 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The Fredericton Pickleball Club is serving up community engagement and boosting the local economy with their accessible courts! #GC
Learn more about this organization and how ACOA made a difference: https://www.canada.ca/en/atlantic-canada-opportunities/campaigns/impacts/fredericton-pickleball.html]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Fall Food Tourism - PEI</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o2cuCMibMNU</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/o2cuCMibMNU?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:16:33 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall is the perfect time to showcase the best of Prince Edward Island through food and music. The region is capitalizing on its distinct strengths and offering authentic cultural experiences to build a sustainable tourism industry that feels welcoming to everyone.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Port Charlottetown - PEI</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UjyCbOcBGTY</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/UjyCbOcBGTY?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:15:09 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Congratulations to Port Charlottetown on another busy cruise ship season, bringing in an estimated 167,000 visitors to Prince Edward Island in 2024. 🚢👋  #GC]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Stratford Waterfront Gathering and Event Space - PEI</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P8cEffqH_4k</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/P8cEffqH_4k?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:13:52 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The Town of Stratford recently announced the grand opening of the Stratford Waterfront Gathering and Event Space. This new infrastructure, supported through ACOA’s Innovative Communities Fund, is part of the community’s vision for a more inclusive, greener, and sustainable future.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Magnetic Hill Zoo - Moncton, NB</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=038i2UHTqmc</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/038i2UHTqmc?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:12:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready for a wild adventure? 🦁🐾
Check out the @MagneticHillZoo, Atlantic Canada’s largest zoo! It is home to 70+ species and is sure to educate and inspire.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Dartmouth Modernization news release</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mz9ynzDzuso</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/mz9ynzDzuso?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Small businesses are powerful drivers of our economy, and this #SmallBusinessWeek, we’re highlighting four Nova Scotia companies receiving support to accelerate their growth and impact.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>2024 Blk Women in Excellence Pitch Competition</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FnWkwDK3vUg</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/FnWkwDK3vUg?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:07:22 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 17 Atlantic Canadian entrepreneurs who competed in Let’s Pitch It 2024 this month. Your ideas and ingenuity are a powerful force. You develop innovative products, deliver vital services, and drive economic growth all around you.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Can we learn to spot disinformation?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=snMkLGziOnA</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/snMkLGziOnA?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:25:52 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Can we learn to spot disinformation? How can people protect themselves against disinformation?

We talked to Kathryn Hill, executive director of MediaSmarts, about digital literacy and how people can learn how to improve their disinformation detection skills. 

To learn more about Canada’s efforts to counter state-sponsored disinformation: https://www.international.gc.ca/world-monde/issues_development-enjeux_developpement/peace_security-paix_securite/combatt-disinformation-desinformation.aspx?lang=eng

Watch Next: https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLI-XuG0q34g1vTEhTCfYtl-80tPNtu5CA&si=rzSRMVpqF8oS95bS

00:55 How to avoid spreading disinformation
02:08 How disinformation works
02:59 The ecosystem of information]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>NLOWE (Newfoundland And Labrador Organization of Women Entrepreneurs) 2024 Annual Conference</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DFs1t-D093w</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/DFs1t-D093w?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:53:34 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The Future is Now! 🔮👩🏽‍💼🌟

NLOWE (@nlowe.org) hosted its 2024 Annual Conference last week in St. John’s, Newfoundland and Labrador, bringing together women entrepreneurs and business leaders from across the province.

NLOWE empowers women by helping them start, grow, and advance in business. Congratulations to the NLOWE team on another successful event!

See inspirational highlights from the conference and learn how ACOA continues to support women in business:]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Maritime Gourmet Mushrooms - Great Village, NS</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e7r5dLAIBz0</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/e7r5dLAIBz0?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[We grow when we help others grow.
 
When Jason Giffin, President of Maritime Gourmet Mushrooms Inc., decided to move his business from Halifax to Great Village, NS, he discovered the #RuralAdvantage – a supportive network of farms, restaurants and retail businesses that helped him establish his operation.

ACOA is part of that network, helping @MaritimeGourmet expand to a new, larger facility in Debert. Now, Maritime Gourmet Mushrooms can help others in return.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #2: Who Were the Porters?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/52bae4d3</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/52bae4d3/151f8563.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:49:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Nova Scotia - World Tourism Day</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z-s1OYDsHMw</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Z-s1OYDsHMw?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 3 Oct 2024 15:08:25 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Winter hibernator or cold-weather adventurer: which one are you?
Whatever the answer, a winter wonderland awaits you in Ingonish, Nova Scotia.
 
Locals and visitors flock to the Cape Breton Highlands when the snow flies, and that’s why 4-season recreation and accommodation is growing in the region.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Saltair Nordic Spa and Wellness - Canning, NS</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzsi3VVrWYw</link><author>ACOACanada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jzsi3VVrWYw?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 3 Oct 2024 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFRoY5IvADtfCf1folzzc-A">ACOACanada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Saltair Nordic is helping to extend the tourism seasonin the Annapolis Valley!

With support from ACOA, owners June Pardy and Jenny Sinclair were able to act on an idea to combine yoga and the spa experience. Saltair Nordic Spa and Wellness provides a local hub for the community and attracts visitors to the area year-round.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is AI Coming For Your Job?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/8b36bff9</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/8b36bff9/074edef7.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 3 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[AI is here and it’s here to stay. Apps like ChatGPT are now allowing us to perform complex tasks with the click of a button.  As we begin to use these new versions of AI, our jobs are destined to change. So, what will an average day of work look like a decade from now? Which jobs will AI impact the most? And is AI coming to replace our jobs altogether?   In this episode, we sat down with AI expert Tahsin Mehdi, an economist in the social analysis and modeling division of Statistics Canada, to answer our questions about how AI will transform our work lives in Canada. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 2 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/958a8685</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/958a8685/8cb11753.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:01:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we explore who the porters were, where they came from, and how they found themselves on the rails. (Episode 2 trailer) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Protecting Workers from Bird Flu</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protecting-workers-from-bird-flu</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode216_ProtectingWorkersFromBirdFlu_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:36:05 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Farms experiencing a surge in bird flu infections can put people who work with poultry and dairy cattle at risk of catching the illness. In this episode, we talk with CCOHS Senior Technical Specialist Matea Kokorovic about measures you can take to protect your workers.Released: September 13, 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Protéger les travailleurs contre la grippe aviaire</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/protger-les-travailleurs-contre-la-grippe-aviaire</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode216_Protger_les_travailleurs_contre_la_grippe_aviaire_working_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:32:29 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Les exploitations qui connaissent une recrudescence des infections par la grippe aviaire exposent les personnes qui travaillent avec les volailles et les bovins laitiers au risque de contracter la maladie. Au cours du présent épisode, nous nous entretenons avec Matea Kokorovic, spécialiste technique principale du Centre canadien d’hygiène et de sécurité au travail au sujet des mesures que vous pouvez prendre pour protéger vos travailleurs.Date de diffusion : 13 septembre 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Unlock your career potential - Insider insights from Tania Levy</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WCRpzak34ok</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/WCRpzak34ok?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 18:55:08 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock your career potential, featuring Enforcement Support Officer Tania Levy.

Version française: https://youtu.be/ormd5M-_5dU]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk #1: Honouring Stanley G. Grizzle - An Activist For Our Times</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/483c1bfa</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/483c1bfa/46a12ede.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:22:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the life of the man who recorded the stories of the porters working on the rails. (Episode 1) ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Stephen Burt, CDO of Canada, invites public servants to AccelerateGOV 2024</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cd79Km1NrYU</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Cd79Km1NrYU?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Stephen Burt, Chief Data Officer of Canada, invites public servants to attend AccelerateGOV conference in Ottawa on October 21, 2024.
Learn from Canadian and international public service digital leaders. 
This event is free for all public servants.
Register today: https://events.globalgovernmentforum.com/accelerategov24?lang=en (globalgovernmentforum.com)]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Episode 1 Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/69f33af4</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/69f33af4/8a4d3c66.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:11:58 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Stanley G. Grizzle, a Canadian Pacific Railway porter for twenty years as well as a celebrated activist, civil servant, and citizenship judge, was also an avid historian who went to great lengths to document and preserve Black History in Canada and beyond. His collection is now held at Library and Archives Canada. Join us as we delve into the man who turned the microphone over to the porters to record their experiences working on the rails. (Episode 1 trailer)]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Porter Talk: Trailer</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/fb5f3d58</link><author>Discover Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/fb5f3d58/542042d8.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:42:21 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover Library and Archives Canada presents “Porter Talk.” This mini-series explores the lived experiences of Black men who laboured as porters for both the Canadian National and Canadian Pacific Railways during the twentieth century. Their voices, along with those of their wives and children, relay stories of both hardship and resilience. (Podcast series trailer)]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/sparking-courageous-conversations-at-work</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode215__CourageousConversations_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 8 Aug 2024 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ Holding courageous conversations in the workplace can help to advance equity, diversity, and inclusion. Learn how to start these discussions, and how they can foster greater understanding, connection, growth, and even healing. Released:  August 8, 2024 -------------------------« Sparking Courageous Conversations at Work »     Tenir des conversations courageuses sur le lieu de travail peut contribuer à faire avancer l’équité, la diversité et l’inclusion. Apprenez comment entamer ces discussions et comment elles peuvent favoriser une meilleure compréhension, une meilleure connexion, une meilleure croissance et même une meilleure guérison.Date de diffusion : 8 août 2024]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Was sind Verzerrungen in der KI? / What is Bias in AI?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kVxVBN5gOxo</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/kVxVBN5gOxo?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 1 Aug 2024 12:46:12 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Dieses Interview mit Saniye Gülser Corat wurde im März 2024 in Wien während einer Expertenrunde zum Internationalen Frauentag gefilmt, die von der Botschaft Kanadas in Österreich zum Thema „Frauen in der Wissenschaft“ organisiert wurde, um die Bedeutung der weiblichen Perspektive in den MINT-Fächern hervorzuheben.

This interview with Saniye Gülser Corat was filmed in March 2024 in Vienna during an expert panel event to highlight International Women’s Day co-organized by the Embassy of Canada to Austria on “Women in Science” to highlight the importance of female perspective in STEM disciplines.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What is Bias in AI?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nsu9TP6CF00</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/nsu9TP6CF00?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 1 Aug 2024 12:45:38 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[This interview with Saniye Gülser Corat was filmed in March 2024 in Vienna during an expert panel event to highlight International Women’s Day co-organized by the Embassy of Canada to Austria on “Women in Science” to highlight the importance of female perspective in STEM disciplines.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Why Economists Are Sounding the Alarm on Productivity</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7b2071ff</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7b2071ff/7f86ea5b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Canada’s workforce is among the most educated in the world. But when it comes to worker productivity, we’ve seen a real slump over the past few years. The quarterly data published by StatCan in June 2024 confirms Canadian workers are continuing to underperform compared to our neighbours to the south. This comes as no surprise to this episode’s guest, Guy Gellatly, Chief Economic Advisor at StatCan. The latest quarterly numbers are a continuation of an on-going decline in Canada’s productivity that economists have been tracking for years.  But what factors influence worker productivity? And why does it matter if Canadians are less productive? As a matter of fact, what even  productivity? In this episode, we asked Guy to help us understand how we got to this point and why it matters for Canadians.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Compliance Case Files: Mergers and Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U7xUOlo8USo</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/U7xUOlo8USo?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Video on Mergers and Acquisitions. Part of the Compliance Bootcamp, a series of learning modules to help professionals stay on the right side of the law.

Disponible en français au : https://youtu.be/tbD_njGdZP8

https://competition-bureau.canada.ca/how-we-foster-competition/education-and-outreach/compliance-bootcamp]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Compliance Case Files: Price-fixing</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-xiJJmuT7LY</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/-xiJJmuT7LY?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:58:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Disponible en français au: https://youtu.be/HfRQRHKw5-4

Video on avoiding price-fixing. Part of lesson 2 of the Compliance Bootcamp, a series of learning modules to help professionals stay on the right side of the law.

https://competition-bureau.canada.ca/how-we-foster-competition/education-and-outreach/compliance-bootcamp]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>A conversation on Canada’s National Action Plan on Women, Peace and Security</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IGYtgaptnR8</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/IGYtgaptnR8?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:27:22 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Minister Joly sat down with Katrina Leclerc to discuss Foundations for Peace: Canada’s national action plan on Women, Peace and Security.

00:00 – 2:47 – Opening remarks
2:48-4:32 – Introduction to Canada’s National Action Plan on Women, Peace and Security
4:36-7:49 - Muzna Dureid’s question
7:50-9:47 - Joseph Akilimali’s question
9 :48-14:46 - Hala Al-Karib’s question
14:47-17:45 - Katrina Leclerc’s question
17 :46-19 :36 – Closing remarks

Learn more about the Action Plan here: https://www.international.gc.ca/world-monde/issues_development-enjeux_developpement/gender_equality-egalite_des_genres/cnap_wps-pnac_fps.aspx?lang=eng

#WomenPeaceSecurity]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Implementing changes to the Competition Act (Bill C-59)</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zs5xNHAqJ0M</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/zs5xNHAqJ0M?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:49:18 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Transcript

Visual:

Title Card: Competition Bureau Canada / Bureau de la concurrence Canada – Implementing changes to the Competition Act

Speaker on-screen: Matthew Boswell, Canada’s Commissioner of Competition.

Audio:
The Government of Canada has recently made a series of important changes to the Competition Act. 
These changes give us stronger tools to take enforcement action and promote competition -- so that all Canadians can benefit from lower prices, better services, and more choice.   
Over the coming months, we will be updating our guidance to give clarity on how and when we’ll take action under the new provisions of the law.   
As a part of this process, we will be holding a series of public consultations.  

Visual: A group of 5 men and women speaking to each other around a table in an office setting.  The man on the left hands a stack of paperwork to the man in the middle. The scene then returns to Matthew.

Audio:
We’re hoping to hear a wide range of perspectives, and we’ll carefully consider all of the feedback we receive. 
In the meantime, we welcome any comments or suggestions that you’d like us to consider.   
These can be submitted through our new Guidance Feedback Form. 
We look forward to hearing from you on these important changes to competition law in Canada. 

Visual: End card: Competition Bureau Canada / Bureau de la concurrence Canada accompanied by the Canadian Flag Government Identifier.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How important is resilience to disinformation?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XalslDFLbLQ</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/XalslDFLbLQ?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:30:01 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[How important is resilience to disinformation? How can people protect themselves against disinformation? How can governments prepare to defend themselves against disinformation?

We talked to Lutz Güllner, head of Strategic Communications at the European External Action Service, about the impact of disinformation on democracies and how countries can protect themselves against it.  
 
To learn more about Canada’s efforts to counter state-sponsored disinformation: https://www.international.gc.ca/world-monde/issues_development-enjeux_developpement/peace_security-paix_securite/combatt-disinformation-desinformation.aspx?lang=eng

CHAPTERS
00:00 Disinformation & Democracy
00:23 How important is resilience to disinformation?
01:45 How can people protect themselves against disinformation?
3:16 How can governments better prepare to defend themselves against disinformation?]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Live now: Watch closing remarks at the #CDBbog54</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tegPqPuYJQw</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/tegPqPuYJQw?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 08:43:43 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Watch the official Opening Ceremony of the #CDBbog54 in Ottawa, Ontario.</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J1oSnhTviFc</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/J1oSnhTviFc?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 02:46:08 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>AI generated scams</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V0dWsv7sptA</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/V0dWsv7sptA?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:28:02 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is an exciting tool that can help us in our everyday lives, but fraudsters can also use it to make their frauds even more convincing. If you believe you’ve come across misleading AI generated content, report it to the Competition Bureau. For more information, check out our consumer alert: The rise of AI: Fraud in the digital age: https://www.canada.ca/en/competition-bureau/news/2024/03/the-rise-of-ai-fraud-in-the-digital-age.html

Transcript

Title/Cover: AI generated scams 

Scene 1: Audio
Sam finds AI technologies helpful for work and school. 
 
Scene 1: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual shows a figure on sitting in a coffee shop on a computer.

Scene 2: Audio
But here’s the thing: Fraudsters can also use AI to target Canadians. 
 
Scene 2: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to close-up of computer screen. On the screen is a social media website and a video pops up on screen.  
 
Scene 3: Audio
One day, Sam spots a sponsored ad with their favorite celebrity endorsing a miracle skin care product.
 
Scene 3: Visual
Image on-screen: The pop up video is enlarged. Visual of a celebrity figure appears on screen holding up a bottle. Stars appear around the bottle. 
 
Scene 4: Audio
Sam is sold and ready to give it a try.
 
Scene 4: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to the figure looking at their computer screen and holding up a credit card. The figure focuses on the computer screen. 
 
Scene 5: Audio
But after paying closer attention, they realize the person in the ad is a fake. Fraudsters can use AI to make fake images, audio, or videos of real people to sell you phony products.
 
Scene 5: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to the computer screen. The word “FAKE” appears next to the celebrity figure. The video zooms out to reveal the celebrity figure in the video is a puppet being controlled by a figure wearing a hoodie. The stars on screen fall. 
 
Scene 6: Audio
Always pay close attention to content you see online before handing over your hard-earned money. 
 
Scene 6: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to the figure looking at the computer screen focused.

Scene 7: Audio
If you come across deceptive content, report it to the Competition Bureau.

Scene 7: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual of the Competition Bureau’s website on a laptop computer animates on screen with text that reads “Competition Bureau Canada”. Text that reads “Complaint Form” animates at the top of the computer screen in the search bar.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Canada and the G7 | 🌍 Exciting News for 2025! 🌟</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kv7_4AhZw04</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/Kv7_4AhZw04?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:37:44 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[🌍 Exciting News for 2025! 🌟

Once again, assuming the G7 Presidency, #Canada is set to host the Leaders Summit. We are thrilled to announce that the Summit will return to the breathtaking Kananaskis, Alberta, a testament to Canada's global leadership and natural beauty. 🍁🏞️

This momentous event provides us with a unique platform to showcase our leadership, foster international collaboration, and highlight the natural beauty of Kananaskis. With its awe-inspiring landscapes and rich cultural heritage, #Kananaskis is the perfect setting for discussions of national and international importance. The decision to hold the Summit in Alberta shows our commitment to inclusivity and unity. Let's seize this opportunity to inspire and shape a better future together. 

Stay tuned for more updates as we gear up for this significant event!

#G7Canada,#G7Kananaskis2025,#ExploreCanada,#GovernmentofCanada,#GOC,#InternationalRelations,#SustainableFuture]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How does artificial intelligence impact the creation of disinformation?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C1jd0TfPQpM</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/C1jd0TfPQpM?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:17:08 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[How does artificial intelligence impact the creation of disinformation? 

We talked to Lutz Güllner, head of Strategic Communications at the European External Action Service, about the impact of disinformation on democracies and how country can protect themselves against it.  
 
To learn more about Canada’s efforts to counter state-sponsored disinformation: https://www.international.gc.ca/world-monde/issues_development-enjeux_developpement/peace_security-paix_securite/combatt-disinformation-desinformation.aspx?lang=eng]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Science vs. food waste</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/7f8e0c6e</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/7f8e0c6e/41a008b7.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Can we make biodegradable plastics using food waste? Can we control disease in crops and eliminate food borne pathogens using just hydrogen peroxide, ozone and UV rays? Yes, we can! Meet the two grand prize winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge – in the novel technology stream -- who proved we can do this and more. Learn how Genecis Bioindustries and Clean Works are fighting food waste and food loss with cutting-edge science. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Exploring the intersection between IP law and the protection of Indigenous knowledge and cultural expressions.</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/exploring-the-intersection-between-ip-law-and-the-protection-of-indigenous-knowledge-and-cultural-expressions-6_dwPtEd</link><author>The Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/7dc0fbc6-bf76-42af-9a5a-54b585cf7862/audio/6d7173e5-5d2c-40ed-9eac-97249d398041/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jun 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What’s an urban forest?</title><link>https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/whats-an-urban-forest</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/1836700347-nrcan-whats-an-urban-forest.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jun 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science">Simply Science</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>It&apos;s Not Easy Bein&apos; Green</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/54f7dce8</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/54f7dce8/a10b6988.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 6 Jun 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[We can try our best, but its not always easy knowing what's best for the environment. The world is complicated, and it isn't as simple as reduce, reuse, recycle—though that's a great place to start!In the immortal words of Kermit the Frog, "It's not easy bein' green."We have two stories exploring that theme. The first is one we made in-house asking just how green our digital world really is, and the second comes from the Simply Science podcast exploring the world of urban forests.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/how-plain-language-improves-workplace-health-and-safety</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode214_PlainLanguage_JocelynPletz_English.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 5 Jun 2024 14:53:52 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[When employers commit to using plain language, they make it easier for workers to do their jobs. They also help to support a more inclusive workplace. In this episode, we talk with plain language expert Jocelyn Pletz about how clear and simple communication can improve health and safety.-------------------------« How Plain Language Improves Workplace Health and Safety »   Lorsque les employeurs s’engagent à utiliser un langage clair, ils facilitent le travail des travailleurs. Ils favorisent aussi l’inclusivité dans le milieu de travail. Dans cet épisode, nous parlerons avec Jocelyn Pletz, spécialiste du langage clair, qui expliquera comment les communications claires et simples peuvent améliorer la santé et la sécurité.Date de diffusion : 5 juin 2024Taille du fichier : 8.2 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Open Government Week</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2X5YxMXvBgI</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/2X5YxMXvBgI?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 4 Jun 2024 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Transcription:

The Government of Canada is dedicated to the principles of open government:
Transparency, Integrity, Accountability, and Public participation.

And to leveraging the open government portal as the door to sharing government information and data with Canadians.

Including information on spending, access to information requests, and more!

Explore open government!]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Grants and Contributions Transformation Initiative: Partner Forum (May 2024)</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=migmWvo9uXk</link><author>Global Affairs Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/migmWvo9uXk?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 18:24:39 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIVMBvs03h74NSdQMH31jKA">Global Affairs Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[On May 21, 2024, external organizations participated in Global Affairs Canada’s virtual Grants and Contributions Transformation Initiative (GCTI) Partner Forum event. Learn more about the GCTI: https://www.international.gc.ca/world-monde/funding-financement/grants-contributions-subventions-contributions.aspx?lang=eng 

Watch the GCTI Partner Forum in French: https://youtu.be/VXUHTgUMsNM]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Fake Online Reviews and Subscription Traps</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jy6e_TDoDYY</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/jy6e_TDoDYY?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:45:29 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[As social media and online shopping have become ever-present in our lives, we are increasingly exposed to the risk of being targeted by fraudsters. If you believe you have come across fake online reviews or have been misled by a free trial offer, report it to the Competition Bureau: https://competition-bureau.canada.ca/contact-competition-bureau-canada/complaint-form

Transcript

Title/Cover: Fake Online Reviews and Subscription Traps 

Scene 1: Audio
Meet Alex.
 
Scene 1: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual shows a figure on screen sitting sideways on a chair in their kitchen. The figure is browsing the internet on their smartphone.
 
Scene 2: Audio
While browsing the internet, they found a streaming service with a one-time payment for exclusive content. 
 
Scene 2: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to close-up of smartphone. Visual of an ad for a streaming app with 50K 5-star ratings with animated text that reads: “SeriousFlicks, Find Exclusive Shows Here”. Visual of the figure's index finger tapping the "Reviews" button on-screen. 
 
Scene 3: Audio
The reviews were great, so they signed up.
 
Scene 3: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual represents scrolling through a list of 5 star reviews and the figure's index finger tapping on the "Subscribe" button on-screen. 2 green dollar signs appear. 
 
Scene 4: Audio
They soon discovered the service was lousy and the reviews were fake.
 
Scene 4: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to the figure visibly frustrated while shaking the smartphone. Visual changes to the smartphone screen with a buffering animation overtop a stream. Visual changes to the list of reviews with the word "FAKE" appearing next to all of them. 
 
Scene 5: Audio
And to their surprise, they had an ongoing subscription they never agreed to.
 
Scene 5: Visual
Image on-screen: Close up of the smartphone and the figure's index finger repeatedly tapping the unsubscribe button. 
 
Scene 6: Audio
This can happen to anyone.
 
Scene 6: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual changes to the figure looking at their phone visibly angry. 
 
Scene 7 Audio
The Competition Bureau enforces laws against deceptive marketing practices. If you suspect deceptive ads, report them to us.
 
Scene 8 Visual
Image on-screen: Visual of the Competition Bureau’s website on a laptop computer animates on screen with text that reads “Competition Bureau Canada”. Text that reads “Complaint Form” animates at the top of the computer screen in the search bar.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Embracing Neurodiversity in the Workplace</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/embracing-neurodiversity-in-the-workplace</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode213_Neurodiversity.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 20:09:44 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ In this episode, we chat with Dr. Marie-Hélène Pelletier, a psychologist and business leader, about embracing neurodiverse conditions such as attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, dyslexia, and autism spectrum disorder, in the workplace.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Faire place à la neurodiversité au travail</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/faire-place-la-neurodiversit-au-travail</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode213_Faire_place__la_neurodiversit_au_travail_French.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 19:58:38 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Dans cet épisode, nous discutons avec Marie-Hélène Pelletier, Ph. D., psychologue et chef des opérations, au sujet d’adaptation à la neurodiversité, comme le trouble d’hyperactivité avec déficit de l’attention, la dyslexie et le trouble du spectre de l’autisme en milieu de travailDate de diffusion : 13 may 2024 Taille du fichier :  8 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Why Food Inflation Is Such a Hard Nut to Crack</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/97b2d26e</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/97b2d26e/2f703e92.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 8 May 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you feeling like it's a little bit harder to bring home the bacon... from the grocery store? The latest data indicate that food prices have mostly stabilized... but why does it feel like the cost of feeding your family is still going up?Today we're talking food inflation with StatCan's resident smart cookie Taylor Mitchell.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How the IP agent profession is regulated</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-the-ip-agent-profession-is-regulated-2LEqe6Zv</link><author>CPATA, College of Patent Agents &amp; Trademark Agents, Canadian Intellectual Property Office, CIPO</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/bd69a14a-17bb-4f9d-b562-95a58d2d0cb5/audio/0b43c574-3324-4a8e-8017-28381ef6786b/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 1 May 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Juda Strawczynski, CEO and Registrar of the College of Patent Agents and Trademark Agents (CPATA) explains how CPATA regulates the IP agent profession, ensuring that patent agents and trademark agents deliver accessible, ethical and expert IP services in Canada.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Challenge accepted!</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/0a6bab0c</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/0a6bab0c/8897684b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:20:54 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Announcing the two winners of the Food Waste Reduction Challenge (Business Models Stream)Two companies took away $1.5 M! Find out who they are. Learn what it took to become the winners of the challenge, and leaders in this new sub-sector. The funds will help the winning companies further expand their success in fighting food waste and reducing greenhouse gases.  And, we’ll give you a glimpse behind the scenes with Dr Jean-Charles Le Vallée, who will share insights into being a jury member of the challenge. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Treasures Revealed: Episode 16</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/81acd6cf</link><author>Library and Archives Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/81acd6cf/d5bc821b.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://library-archives.canada.ca/eng/collection/engage-learn/podcast/pages/podcasts.aspx">Discover Library and Archives Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[The hammering of the last spike into the Canadian Pacific Railway expanded access to the nation immeasurably, physically and symbolically connecting it from coast to coast. While seen as a victory in the dominant narrative of Canada, it served as a catalyst for the mass displacement of Indigenous peoples and the exploitation and even death of labourers involved in the construction of the railway. Join us as Marcelle Cinq-Mars delves into the historic image depicting this moment, and we reflect on the real human cost that was paid in the name of progress.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>It&apos;s 8 pm...Do You Know What Your Kids Are Googling?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/8710dcf9</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/8710dcf9/cb577436.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 9 Apr 2024 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[StatCan released new analysis into the online culture our kids are growing up in, and it’s far from the best of all possible worlds: misinformation, bullying, violence… and worse.Analyst Rachel Tsitomeneas joins us to dive into the findings. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/day-of-mourning-melanie-kowalski-flemings-story</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode212_Melanie_Kowalski-Fleming_DayOfMourning.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 8 Apr 2024 14:07:32 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA["Mark was not one to go to the hospital. If he could duct tape or crazy glue it to fix it, he would. This was so much more than what duct tape or crazy glue could fix.” Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s life changed forever the day her husband fell off a ladder at work. Hear her powerful story. -------------------------« Day of Mourning: Melanie Kowalski-Fleming’s Story »« Mark n’était pas du genre à aller à l’hôpital. S’il pouvait régler le problème avec du ruban adhésif ou de la colle, il le faisait. Mais cette fois, le ruban adhésif et la colle n’y pouvaient rien. » La vie de Melanie Kowalski-Fleming a changé pour toujours le jour où son mari est tombé d’une échelle au travail. Écoutez son histoire percutante.Date de diffusion : 8 avril 2024Taille du fichier : 7.5 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>What innovators need to know about the Competition Bureau</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/what-innovators-need-to-know-about-the-competition-bureau-Tjj37JmI</link><author>Canadian Bureau of Competition, Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/02a3fbe4-ec94-454b-8f88-e8e915b5d2ff/audio/c37de1ae-aee8-45d2-8983-0032d1bf6350/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 3 Apr 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Alan Gunderson, senior economist and coordinator at the Economic Analysis Directorate at the Competition Bureau explains the Bureau’s mandate and actions when it comes to intellectual property.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Tax time: What older Canadians and caregivers need to know</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/tax-time-what-older-canadians-and-caregivers-need-to-know-u7OhrWN9</link><author>Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/18f63d87-fb0c-4903-af7e-e088670d5494/audio/01714c8e-0da8-4388-b47e-52407fcdd27b/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the importance of filing your taxes on time, what tax credits are available for older Canadians and caregivers for the 2023 filing season, tips to help with filing, important dates and the CRA’s toll-free number, 1-800-959-8281.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Période des impôts : Ce que les aînés canadiens et les proches aidants doivent savoir</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/periode-des-impots-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-et-les-proches-aidants-doivent-savoir-SbfA8SpQ</link><author>Charles Drouin, Cathy Khoury</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/0a89e7b2-4fbf-4612-b70b-ab532098dcd6/audio/4c4fd677-5fb8-498e-be3b-f20c6524efae/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:19:26 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Découvrez l’importance de produire votre déclaration de revenus dans les temps et quels crédits d’impôt sont offerts aux aînés canadiens et aux proches aidants pour la période des impôts 2023. Obtenez également des conseils pour vous aider à produire votre déclaration et apprenez quelles sont les dates importantes. Voici le numéro sans frais de l’ARC : 1-800-959-7383.Page Facebook des Aînés au Canada - https://www.facebook.com/AinesauCanada/]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency Investment Fraud</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QmLnUNA3iik</link><author>Competition Bureau Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/QmLnUNA3iik?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:06:42 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWEkolOpjOruSK_lbGuhfVA">Competition Bureau Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Investment fraud, including cryptocurrency fraud, takes many forms, but they all have one thing in common – the big lie that you can make tons of fast cash! If you believe you have been misled or think you’ve seen a cryptocurrency investment fraud, report it to the Competition Bureau: https://competition-bureau.canada.ca/contact-competition-bureau-canada/complaint-form

Transcript 

Title/Cover: Cryptocurrency Investment Fraud 

Scene 1: Audio
Meet Jo, like many Canadians…

Scene 1: Visual 
Image on-screen: Visual shows a figure on screen sitting sideways on a chair in their living room. The figure is scrolling through social media feed on their device.

Scene 2: Audio
…they’re tempted by cryptocurrency’s fantastic financial potential.

Scene 2: Visual 
Image on-screen: Visual changes to close-up of scrolling, zoom in on a flashy investment ad with animated text that reads: “400% return in 2 weeks! Cancel anytime. INVEST NOW before it’s too late.” Visuals of crypto currency symbols display near the bottom of the screen. Hand animates into frame and a finger presses on the “INVEST NOW Before it’s too late” button.

Scene 3: Audio
Seduced by promises of high profits and guaranteed returns, Jo takes the “plunge.”

Scene 3: Visual 
Image on-screen: Visual of the figure holding their mobile phone in one hand and in the other hand, their credit card to transfer funds. Animated text on the right side appears “- $15,000” in red with an arrow pointing down to animated crypto currency symbols to indicate that they are investing real money in cryptocurrency on the fraudulent platform.

Scene 4: Audio
But over time, Jo will realize that online ads exaggerated potential earnings and their guarantees were fake.

Scene 4: Visual 
Image on-screen: Visual of an arrow rises through graph with five-star reviews animate below with text that reads “Just made $10k in a week! That’s totally legit. $$” and text that reads “The ultimate crypto investment solution!!!”. As the visual of the arrow on the graph continues to rise, the word “FAKE” animates over the graph and gets bigger and smaller a few times as a alert warning to the viewer. 

Scene 5: Audio
In the world of cryptocurrency…

Scene 5: Visual 
Image on-screen: Visual of the figure’s index finger clicking on a button with on screen text that reads “WITHDRAW”. 

Scene 6: Audio
…fraudsters are exploiting your lack of knowledge...

Scene 6: Visual
Once clicked, the button changes to red with animated text that reads “FAILED” on screen

Scene 7: Audio
 …with deceptive tactics like phony reviews and fake celebrity endorsements.

Scene 7: Visual
Image on-screen: Scene changes to a close-up of the figure looking down at their mobile phone with a surprised expression on their face. Their expression quickly changes to a frown discovering that their money disappeared, they cannot withdraw the cryptocurrency they thought they purchased, and they have been defrauded.

Scene 8: Audio
If you come across misleading investment ads report them to the Competition Bureau.

Scene 8: Visual
Image on-screen: Visual of the Competition Bureau’s website on a laptop computer animates on screen with text that reads “Competition Bureau Canada”. Text that reads “Complaint Form” animates at the top of the computer screen in the search bar.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How does the government make sure that you get the best results from taxpayer dollars?</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qMJ15PRQ2e4</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/qMJ15PRQ2e4?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:50:30 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[How does the government make sure that you get the best results from taxpayer dollars? 
Video produced by: TBS Communications
This video was recorded in a bilingual format, but the transcript is found in both languages below.

Comment le gouvernement obtient les meilleurs résultats possibles avec l’argent des contribuables?
Vidéo produite par : Communications du SCT
Cette vidéo a été enregistrée dans un format bilingue, mais la transcription se trouve dans les deux langues ci-dessous.

---

English Transcription:

Hi everyone! Anita here. 
You might wonder how the government makes sure that you get the best results from taxpayer dollars. 
That’s my job as President of the Treasury Board.
We make sure that we have good management of our employees, of taxpayer dollars, and of technology.
I chair the Treasury Board, Canada's oldest and only legislated Cabinet committee.
The Treasury Board reviews and approves spending plans proposed by departments and keeps an eye on how government programs are carried out to ensure accountability.
The Treasury Board is the employer of more than 250,000 employees across 70 organizations.
It is supported by a secretariat, which I also manage.
The Treasury Board Secretariat develops policies, and it sets out the strategic direction for the rest of the government in many areas of administration, including financial management, communications, people management, and regulations.
We are focussed on ensuring that:
 - Your tax dollars are managed carefully and focused on what matters most to you.
 - You have access to high-quality, modern, and reliable government services.
 - And that you can count on a high-performing, diverse, and dedicated public service that ensures that we are serving Canada and Canadians.
In short, we ensure that the government is well managed so that Canadians are well served.
Thank you for keeping me company today.
One more thing I love about being at Treasury Board, is that I get to interact and communicate with my colleagues every single day. I'm off to Treasury Board now, have a great day!

Transcription en français :

Bonjour tout le monde! Ici Anita. Vous vous demandez peut-être comment le gouvernement obtient les meilleurs résultats possibles avec l’argent des contribuables? 
Cela fait partie de mon travail en tant que présidente du Conseil du Trésor.
Je veille, avec mon équipe, à la bonne gestion de nos effectifs, de l’argent des contribuables et de la technologie.
Je préside le Conseil du Trésor, le plus ancien comité du Cabinet du Canada et le seul établi par la loi.
Le Conseil du Trésor examine et approuve les plans de dépenses proposés par les ministères et surveille la manière dont les programmes gouvernementaux sont exécutés afin de veiller à la responsabilisation.
Le Conseil du Trésor est l'employeur de plus de 250 000 fonctionnaires répartis dans 70 organisations.
Il est soutenu par un secrétariat, que je dirige également.
Le Secrétariat du Conseil du Trésor élabore des politiques et définit l’orientation stratégique pour le reste du gouvernement dans de nombreux domaines de l’administration, dont la gestion financière, les communications, la gestion des personnes et la réglementation.
Il veille à ce :
 - que l’argent des contribuables soit géré avec soin et affecté à ce qui compte le plus pour vous;
 - que vous ayez accès à des services gouvernementaux de haute qualité, modernes et fiables;
 - que vous puissiez compter sur une fonction publique performante, diversifiée et dévouée, qui veille à ce que nous soyons au service du Canada et de sa population.
Bref, le SCT veille à ce que le gouvernement soit bien géré pour que la population canadienne soit bien servie.
Merci de votre présence à mes côtés aujourd’hui.
Une autre chose que j’aime bien de mon travail au Conseil du Trésor, c’est que j’ai l’occasion d’interagir et de communiquer avec mes collègues tous les jours. Je vous laisse à présent pour me rendre au Conseil du Trésor, et je vous souhaite une excellente journée!]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Combattre la fraude en la reconnaissant : Ce que les aînés canadiens doivent savoir</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/combattre-la-fraude-en-la-reconnaissant-ce-que-les-aines-canadiens-doivent-savoir-45XxdLpc</link><author>Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/68d929e0-f1da-4c9c-b21c-8dc3b517f4ee/audio/08552b08-191a-4913-9b01-141f73c441a5/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:50:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury et Jeffrey Horncastle parlent du Centre antifraude du Canada, des principales fraudes envers les aînés canadiens, des mesures à prendre si vous êtes victime de fraude et de l’importance de signaler une fraude au Centre antifraude du Canada, soit en ligne ou en appelant le numéro sans frais 1-888-495-8501.Centre antifraude du Canada : Mois de la prévention de la fraude :Guide de sécurité à l’intention des aînés, GRC :]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Fighting fraud with knowledge: What older Canadians need to know</title><link>https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/episodes/fighting-fraud-with-knowledge-what-older-canadians-need-to-know-74Z9Ffwc</link><author>Cathy Khoury, Jeff Horncastle</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/10db0d51-dfba-42b0-8b33-3ad55876639c/episodes/54c95db9-0ac5-4904-aed0-49469626d84a/audio/b3aa55bd-4ee5-43f7-87b6-920c070d14be/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=9Uo30mEr" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:49:55 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://employment-and-social-development-canada.simplecast.com/">Employment and Social Development Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Cathy Khoury and Jeffrey Horncastle discuss the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC), tops scams targeting older Canadians, what to do if you have been a victim of fraud and the importance of reporting fraud to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre online or by calling the toll-free number at 1-888-495-8501.Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre: RCMP Seniors Guide to Safety and Security:]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How Do You Say &quot;Language Revitalization&quot; in Cree?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/bd75c457</link><author>Statistics Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/bd75c457/f67c653e.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://www.statcan.gc.ca/en/sc/podcasts">Eh Sayers</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[More than 70 distinct Indigenous languages are spoken by First Nations people, Métis and Inuit in Canada, but these languages are under threat. In this episode, we speak with Randy Morin and Belinda kakiyosēw Daniels, who share their knowledge of the Cree language with learners at the Nêhiyawak Language Experience, about the wisdom encoded in Indigenous languages, as well as the opportunities for these languages and the barriers they face. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Comprendre les effets de la sensibilité aux parfums</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/comprendre-les-effets-de-la-sensibilit-aux-parfums</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode211_Comprendre_les_effets_de_la_sensibilit__aux_parfums.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Pour certains travailleurs, l’eau de Cologne et les crèmes à mains peuvent sentir bon, mais pour leurs collègues qui présentent une sensibilité aux parfums, elles peuvent avoir des effets désagréables pour la santé. En fait, les réactions aux parfums, comme les maux de tête, les démangeaisons oculaires et les difficultés respiratoires, sont un problème de santé, et elles sont considérées comme une déficience au sens de la Loi canadienne sur les droits de la personne.   Date de diffusion : 18 mars 2024  Taille du fichier : 3.3 MB]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Making Sense of Scent Sensitivities</title><link>https://ccohs.libsyn.com/making-sense-of-scent-sensitivities</link><author>chris.keen@ccohs.ca (chris.keen@ccohs.ca)</author><enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/ccohs/Episode211_ScentsSensitivites.mp3?dest-id=32116" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="http://ccohs.libsyn.com/">CCOHS Podcasts</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[ While the scent of cologne or hand lotion may be pleasant to some, for co-workers with sensitivities to fragrances, they may have unpleasant health effects. In fact, reactions to scents, such as headaches, itchy eyes, and difficulty breathing, are a medical condition and recognized disability under the Canada Human Rights Act.  ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is that a robot in your field?</title><link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/a5bf9d8e</link><author>Agriculture and Agri-food Canada</author><enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a5bf9d8e/3ef448b2.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://agriculture.canada.ca/en/agri-info/first-sixteen-podcast">The First Sixteen</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Ag-robotics specialists Chuck Baresich believes you’ll have a robot in your field sooner than you think.  What will they do? How will they add value to your farm? Chuck paints a picture of that future. And what is the government doing to help the agricultural sector be ready for those robots? Marco Valicenti, Director General of Innovation Programs Directorate and Brett Maxwell, Director of Strategic Policy Branch explain how Agriculture and Agri-Food Canada’s programs are enabling that future.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Is natural hydrogen the solution?</title><link>https://soundcloud.com/nrcan/is-natural-hydrogen-the-solution</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/1769171136-nrcan-is-natural-hydrogen-the-solution.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.nrcan.gc.ca/simply-science">Simply Science</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Happy International Women’s Day! Bonne Journée internationale de la femme!</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBAhOVsoj74</link><author>TBS Canada</author><category>youtube</category><enclosure url="https://www.youtube.com/v/tBAhOVsoj74?version=3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Fri, 8 Mar 2024 14:12:40 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCV7uvs-FoatgAuyzjpJTS3g">TBS Canada</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[Video produced by: TBS Communications
This video was recorded in a bilingual format, but the transcript is found in both languages below.

Vidéo produite par : Communications du SCT
Cette vidéo a été enregistrée dans un format bilingue, mais la transcription se trouve dans les deux langues ci-dessous.

---

English Transcription:

Even when it seems impossible. Remember that women are breaking glass ceilings across our country and throughout our world, and you are no different. You can succeed too. 

[This year’s theme is “Invest in Women: Accelerate Progress”. What does this mean to you?]
I work in STEM, specifically in cybersecurity. These fields tend to perpetuate a male-dominated culture. So, giving women greater access to pursue cybersecurity
education would help to accelerate progress. 
We must work hard, but we must also have friends and laugh, because it’s important not only to achieve objectives and goals, but also to have friendships.
We must find concrete and relevant ways to support women, invest in them, and ensure their success. 

[Who inspired you to be a leader, and why?]
Definitely my mother. She used to tell us to reach for the stars, the world is our oyster, and her voice is always in my ear. Whenever I'm having a bad day, especially, as she really inspired me to keep on going.

[What advice would you give to your younger self?]
Don't be afraid to step outside of your comfort zone. Calculated risk can lead to growth and new opportunities. Also, don't fear failure. Instead, see it as a learning opportunity.

[What words of wisdom do you have for the next generation of female leaders?]
Don’t compare yourself to others. There is no one way to become a leader, and there is no singular mold to become a leader.  Do your best and always encourage others to do the same. Keep on trying. Never give up. Believe in yourself.

--

Transcription en français :

Même lorsque cela semble impossible, rappelez-vous que les femmes brisent les plafonds de verre partout au pays et dans le monde entier, et vous ne faites pas exception. Vous pouvez réussir aussi. 

[Le thème de cette année est « Investir en faveur des femmes :  accélérer le rythme ». Qu'est-ce que cela signifie pour vous ?]
Je travaille dans le domaine des STIM, plus particulièrement en cybersécurité. Ces domaines ont tendance à perpétuer une culture dominée par les hommes. Ainsi, le fait de donner aux femmes un meilleur accès aux études en cybersécurité permettrait d’accélérer les progrès. 
On doit travailler fort, mais aussi on doit avoir des amis et de rire, parce que c'est important d'accomplir les objectifs de buts, mais aussi d'avoir des amis ensembles.
Nous devons trouver des moyens concrets et significatifs pour soutenir les femmes, investir en eux, et assurer leur réussite.

[Qui vous a incité à devenir une leader, et pourquoi ?]
Sans aucun doute, ma mère. Elle nous disait d’atteindre les sommets, que le monde nous appartient. J’entends toujours sa voix. Lorsque je passe une mauvaise journée; 
surtout qu’elle m’a vraiment encouragée à ne pas lâcher. 

[Si vous pouviez remonter le temps, quel conseil donneriez-vous à une plus jeune version de vous-même?]
N’aie pas peur de sortir de ta zone de confort. Les risques calculés peuvent favoriser la croissance et ouvrir de nouvelles perspectives. Ne crains pas non plus l’échec. Vois-le plutôt comme une occasion d’apprentissage. 

[Quelles paroles de sagesse avez-vous pour la prochaine génération de femmes dirigeantes ?]
Ne vous comparez pas aux autres. Il n'y a pas de voie unique pour devenir un leader, et il n'y a pas de moule défini pour devenir un leader. Faites de votre mieux
et encouragez tout le temps les autres de faire le même. Tiens bon.  Ne baisse jamais les bras. Aie confiance en toi.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How does IP fit into the world of scientific research and experimental development?</title><link>https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/episodes/how-does-ip-fit-into-the-world-of-scientific-research-and-experimental-development-KJ3yT3ka</link><author>Canada Revenue Agency, The Canadian Intellectual Property Office</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/4e91d387-239c-4b03-b1ce-46a2386deb1f/episodes/6265bedc-d3df-40c7-9411-c6d07ad4f1b0/audio/3340bdc5-461c-4494-adfb-af6b9b0f8ac1/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;feed=Zd3oeWec" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Wed, 6 Mar 2024 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://canadian-ip-voices.simplecast.com/">Canadian IP voices</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[David Arsenault, Atlantic Regional Manager for the Canada Revenue Agency's Scientific Research and Experimental Development (SR&ED) Tax Incentive Program, demystifies the parallel worlds of R&D and IP from an SR&ED tax incentive program perspective.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Episode 3: Platform economy and you!</title><link>https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-3-en.mp3</link><author></author><enclosure url="https://www.canada.ca/content/dam/cra-arc/newsroom/pdcsts/txlgy-episode-3-en.mp3" length="" type=""/><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><source url="https://www.canada.ca/en/revenue-agency/news/cra-multimedia-library/podcasts.html">Taxology – The Official Canada Revenue Agency Podcast</source><content:encoded><![CDATA[It's easy to get lost in an internet rabbit hole when trying to learn about the "platform economy" and what it means for your taxes. Whether you're a rideshare driver, a video game streamer, or a social media influencer, this episode has something for you! Originally recorded in 2023.]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>